[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 22, "question": "From what we now believe, Dzhokhar Tsarnaev may have told the investigators in written answers, is that right?", "question_tokens": ["From", "what", "we", "now", "believe", ",", "Dzhokhar", "Tsarnaev", "may", "have", "told", "the", "investigators", "in", "written", "answers", ",", "is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 23, "answer": "That's right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dzhokhar Tsarnaev"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "What was he like in those early days?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "he", "like", "in", "those", "early", "days", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "He was nice, funny.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "nice", ",", "funny", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "Did you ever meet him?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "meet", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "You then went to his Twitter, saw his cryptic tweets, and at that point, did alarm bells ring for you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "then", "went", "to", "his", "Twitter", ",", "saw", "his", "cryptic", "tweets", ",", "and", "at", "that", "point", ",", "did", "alarm", "bells", "ring", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "NN", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "Had they been monitoring your Facebook?", "question_tokens": ["Had", "they", "been", "monitoring", "your", "Facebook", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tamerlan"]}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "What was he like?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "he", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "Well, during that trip, I noticed Tamerlan was a little bit of a flashy guy, really sharp dresser, really confident in his abilities as a boxer.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "during", "that", "trip", ",", "I", "noticed", "Tamerlan", "was", "a", "little", "bit", "of", "a", "flashy", "guy", ",", "really", "sharp", "dresser", ",", "really", "confident", "in", "his", "abilities", "as", "a", "boxer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "And he was a good boxer?", "question_tokens": ["And", "he", "was", "a", "good", "boxer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "He was.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "For some reason in the second tournament, the Golden Gloves, he couldn't travel with the team, so I thought it was because he wasn't allowed to represent the United States, but I can't say for sure.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "some", "reason", "in", "the", "second", "tournament", ",", "the", "Golden", "Gloves", ",", "he", "could", "n't", "travel", "with", "the", "team", ",", "so", "I", "thought", "it", "was", "because", "he", "was", "n't", "allowed", "to", "represent", "the", "United", "States", ",", "but", "I", "ca", "n't", "say", "for", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", ":", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ":", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "RB", "VB", "RBR", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "Did he ever talk to you about religion or politics?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "ever", "talk", "to", "you", "about", "religion", "or", "politics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "He was definitely big into -- the second year I met him, he was a lot -- talked a lot about his faith, just it seemed to really be more about what he was about, his character.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "definitely", "big", "into", "--", "the", "second", "year", "I", "met", "him", ",", "he", "was", "a", "lot", "--", "talked", "a", "lot", "about", "his", "faith", ",", "just", "it", "seemed", "to", "really", "be", "more", "about", "what", "he", "was", "about", ",", "his", "character", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "Did he become more fearful of America or authority?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "become", "more", "fearful", "of", "America", "or", "authority", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "I just noticed that he seemed more humble.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "noticed", "that", "he", "seemed", "more", "humble", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "What was your reaction when you discovered that he had been involved in this terrible atrocity?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "reaction", "when", "you", "discovered", "that", "he", "had", "been", "involved", "in", "this", "terrible", "atrocity", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "I mean, I was saddened by the news like everyone else from this city.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "was", "saddened", "by", "the", "news", "like", "everyone", "else", "from", "this", "city", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Friday"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Martin Luther King Jr."]}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "From all that you've now gleaned about what went on with him, were we seeing somebody who was being radicalized very quickly?", "question_tokens": ["From", "all", "that", "you", "'ve", "now", "gleaned", "about", "what", "went", "on", "with", "him", ",", "were", "we", "seeing", "somebody", "who", "was", "being", "radicalized", "very", "quickly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "I'm not sure I can answer that question but definitely someone standing up in a Friday prayer and questioning a preacher who is talking about Martin Luther King Jr. might draw some flags but I don't think would necessitate calling law enforcement.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "sure", "I", "can", "answer", "that", "question", "but", "definitely", "someone", "standing", "up", "in", "a", "Friday", "prayer", "and", "questioning", "a", "preacher", "who", "is", "talking", "about", "Martin", "Luther", "King", "Jr.", "might", "draw", "some", "flags", "but", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "would", "necessitate", "calling", "law", "enforcement", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "TO", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "With regards to what?", "question_tokens": ["With", "regards", "to", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "TO", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Well, to what's happened.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "to", "what", "'s", "happened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "Our reaction to what?", "question_tokens": ["Our", "reaction", "to", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "TO", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "Your reaction to the discovery that somebody attending one of the mosques has been the perpetrator of this appalling bombing.", "answer_tokens": ["Your", "reaction", "to", "the", "discovery", "that", "somebody", "attending", "one", "of", "the", "mosques", "has", "been", "the", "perpetrator", "of", "this", "appalling", "bombing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "And Jason, do we know how long they are going to carry on talking to him for?", "question_tokens": ["And", "Jason", ",", "do", "we", "know", "how", "long", "they", "are", "going", "to", "carry", "on", "talking", "to", "him", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "Well, you know, that is the big question here.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "that", "is", "the", "big", "question", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jason"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jason Carroll"]}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "Piers?", "question_tokens": ["Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "Jason Carroll, thank you very much.", "answer_tokens": ["Jason", "Carroll", ",", "thank", "you", "very", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "Piers, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "I'm sorry, Senator Ball.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "sorry", ",", "Senator", "Ball", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "Do you still believe that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "believe", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "How you going to torture him?", "question_tokens": ["How", "you", "going", "to", "torture", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "I mean, dude, you're talking to a guy that supports death penalty for cop killers, terrorists.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "dude", ",", "you", "'re", "talking", "to", "a", "guy", "that", "supports", "death", "penalty", "for", "cop", "killers", ",", "terrorists", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "Yes, but how would you torture him?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "how", "would", "you", "torture", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "Piers, I would support -- I'm talking about me.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "I", "would", "support", "--", "I", "'m", "talking", "about", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 224, "question": "Would you play cards with Osama bin Laden?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "play", "cards", "with", "Osama", "bin", "Laden", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "It's really a question -", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "really", "a", "question", "-"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Osama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "What would you do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "Let me put this to you.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "put", "this", "to", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 255, "question": "Would you as a politician want to bring that in as a standard matter of practice in your country, yes or no?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "as", "a", "politician", "want", "to", "bring", "that", "in", "as", "a", "standard", "matter", "of", "practice", "in", "your", "country", ",", "yes", "or", "no", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "What I am saying is that as an individual --", "answer_tokens": ["What", "I", "am", "saying", "is", "that", "as", "an", "individual", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 257, "question": "Yes or no?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", "or", "no", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "If given the opportunity --", "answer_tokens": ["If", "given", "the", "opportunity", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "Am I wrong?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "You're not wrong.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'re", "not", "wrong", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Watertown"], "TIME": ["12:25 a.m."]}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "CD", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "In terms of the way it went on for you as the week went on, were there moments when you felt we're not going to catch this guy?", "question_tokens": ["In", "terms", "of", "the", "way", "it", "went", "on", "for", "you", "as", "the", "week", "went", "on", ",", "were", "there", "moments", "when", "you", "felt", "we", "'re", "not", "going", "to", "catch", "this", "guy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", ",", "VBD", "EX", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "Well, we were right at it right from the beginning with our officers there at 12:25 a.m. in the back street of Watertown.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "were", "right", "at", "it", "right", "from", "the", "beginning", "with", "our", "officers", "there", "at", "12:25", "a.m.", "in", "the", "back", "street", "of", "Watertown", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "Is this your understanding?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "your", "understanding", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "I'm hearing all kinds of different things.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "hearing", "all", "kinds", "of", "different", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "This is quite remarkable technology that you now have at your disposal, isn't it, in these situations?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "quite", "remarkable", "technology", "that", "you", "now", "have", "at", "your", "disposal", ",", "is", "n't", "it", ",", "in", "these", "situations", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "Is that your understanding?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "your", "understanding", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "How are they all bearing up now, now that it's over?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "they", "all", "bearing", "up", "now", ",", "now", "that", "it", "'s", "over", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "VBG", "RP", "RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "You know, we've been together.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "we", "'ve", "been", "together", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Do you know what the situation is with regard to that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "what", "the", "situation", "is", "with", "regard", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "No, I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "Can you shed any light on what was going on then, who these people were?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "shed", "any", "light", "on", "what", "was", "going", "on", "then", ",", "who", "these", "people", "were", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "RB", ",", "WP", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "EVEAU: Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["EVEAU", ":", "Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "What would you have recommended?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "have", "recommended", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "It shouldn't really be much of a debate.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "should", "n't", "really", "be", "much", "of", "a", "debate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "When you heard the state senator on earlier demanding the right to torture this man, what was your reaction to that?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "heard", "the", "state", "senator", "on", "earlier", "demanding", "the", "right", "to", "torture", "this", "man", ",", "what", "was", "your", "reaction", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJR", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "Come on.", "answer_tokens": ["Come", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "We know President Bush sanctioned waterboarding, right?", "question_tokens": ["We", "know", "President", "Bush", "sanctioned", "waterboarding", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bush"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "Is that correct?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "correct", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "Correct.", "answer_tokens": ["Correct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "What do you say to them, given that he is an American citizen who committed a crime on American soil?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "them", ",", "given", "that", "he", "is", "an", "American", "citizen", "who", "committed", "a", "crime", "on", "American", "soil", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "What I say to them is that, I mean, the rough stuff, let's put that aside for a minute.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "I", "say", "to", "them", "is", "that", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "the", "rough", "stuff", ",", "let", "'s", "put", "that", "aside", "for", "a", "minute", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "So they can do that at any time, even after they have read him his Miranda rights?", "question_tokens": ["So", "they", "can", "do", "that", "at", "any", "time", ",", "even", "after", "they", "have", "read", "him", "his", "Miranda", "rights", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "PRP$", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "Yes, that's my view.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "that", "'s", "my", "view", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "NN", "PRP", "CC", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "So the Miranda rights changes nothing in terms of their ability to interrogate?", "question_tokens": ["So", "the", "Miranda", "rights", "changes", "nothing", "in", "terms", "of", "their", "ability", "to", "interrogate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "What it changes is their ability to question him and use any statement that he makes.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "it", "changes", "is", "their", "ability", "to", "question", "him", "and", "use", "any", "statement", "that", "he", "makes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "Whether they're attached to anybody in Chechnya, for example, of an Islamic fundamentalist nature, et cetera, et cetera, how far can you go in terms of eliciting that information from somebody like him in his position once he's had his Miranda rights read to him, as he now has?", "question_tokens": ["Whether", "they", "'re", "attached", "to", "anybody", "in", "Chechnya", ",", "for", "example", ",", "of", "an", "Islamic", "fundamentalist", "nature", ",", "et", "cetera", ",", "et", "cetera", ",", "how", "far", "can", "you", "go", "in", "terms", "of", "eliciting", "that", "information", "from", "somebody", "like", "him", "in", "his", "position", "once", "he", "'s", "had", "his", "Miranda", "rights", "read", "to", "him", ",", "as", "he", "now", "has", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "RB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NNP", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "My view is you can go as far as you think it's productive to go.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "view", "is", "you", "can", "go", "as", "far", "as", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "productive", "to", "go", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Chechnya"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", ":", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "Does he have any kind of defense you could at the moment draw up?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "have", "any", "kind", "of", "defense", "you", "could", "at", "the", "moment", "draw", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "Well, he's going to -- obviously the mitigation strategy is my big brother made me do it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "'s", "going", "to", "--", "obviously", "the", "mitigation", "strategy", "is", "my", "big", "brother", "made", "me", "do", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "I mean, was is the gut feeling you're getting from the way this is playing out?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "was", "is", "the", "gut", "feeling", "you", "'re", "getting", "from", "the", "way", "this", "is", "playing", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "The gut feeling I'm getting, of course, he is blaming it all on big brother.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "gut", "feeling", "I", "'m", "getting", ",", "of", "course", ",", "he", "is", "blaming", "it", "all", "on", "big", "brother", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "TO", "VBG", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "Is there enough there already, do you think, that this is an open and shut criminal case on their complicity in the bombing?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "enough", "there", "already", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "that", "this", "is", "an", "open", "and", "shut", "criminal", "case", "on", "their", "complicity", "in", "the", "bombing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "RB", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "AVIN: I think if I were the prosecutor, I'd feel pretty comfortable at this particular point in time, no matter what he had to say once Mirandized or prior to being Mirandized.", "answer_tokens": ["AVIN", ":", "I", "think", "if", "I", "were", "the", "prosecutor", ",", "I", "'d", "feel", "pretty", "comfortable", "at", "this", "particular", "point", "in", "time", ",", "no", "matter", "what", "he", "had", "to", "say", "once", "Mirandized", "or", "prior", "to", "being", "Mirandized", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "Have there been any failings there that you can see?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "there", "been", "any", "failings", "there", "that", "you", "can", "see", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "EX", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "I think it is a very difficult set of circumstances.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "is", "a", "very", "difficult", "set", "of", "circumstances", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130422pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "Or do you think it is more likely that the older brother, when he went back to Russia, had some kind of contact, perhaps in Chechnya, with some pretty nasty people?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "do", "you", "think", "it", "is", "more", "likely", "that", "the", "older", "brother", ",", "when", "he", "went", "back", "to", "Russia", ",", "had", "some", "kind", "of", "contact", ",", "perhaps", "in", "Chechnya", ",", "with", "some", "pretty", "nasty", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "I still have a big question mark in my mind about that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "still", "have", "a", "big", "question", "mark", "in", "my", "mind", "about", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Russia", "Chechnya"]}}]